https://www.1stcommercialcredit.com/terms-and-conditions/

Terms and ConditionsOver 18 Years in BusinessRecent Transactions
$350,000Clerical Staffing Agency
$1.2 MillionOil Field HaulerPrivacyAt 1stCommercialCredit.com. 1st CommercialCredit.co.uk and 1st CommercialCredit.ca (Sites), (owned and operated by 1st Commercial Credit, LLC of Austin TX) we strive to develop innovative services to better serve our site visitors and customers. We recognize privacy is an important issue and we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in the highest regard.The following principles apply to the personal information we ask for and that you provide on our web site. Personal information is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address when you apply for a free account.Data Collection1st Commercial Credit Sites collects limited non-personally identifying information your browser makes available whenever you visit a website. This log information includes your Internet Protocol address (IP), browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visits and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.CookiesUpon your first visit a 1st Commercial Credit Site, a cookie is sent to your computer which uniquely identifies your browser. A cookie is a small text file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. 1st Commercial Credit's Sites uses cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.Information sharing1st Commercial Credit does not rent or sell your personal information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent.Information SecurityWe take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.We restrict access to your personally identifying information to only those who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.Changes to this PolicyPlease note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.Web Site Usage PolicyBy using this web site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Site Usage Policy. 1st Commercial Credit reserves the right to change the terms of Site Usage Policy or to modify features of 1stCommercialCredit.com at any time. By using this web site, you agree to be bound by such changes.Usage and PermissionsAll content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, images, audio clips, and digital downloads, is the property of 1st Commercial Credit, or its content suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws. You must abide by all additional copyright notices or restrictions contained in the print versions of our publications and research.You may not copy, reproduce, distribute, publish, enter into a database, display, perform, modify, create derivative works, or transmit any content on 1stCommercialCredit.com, except that you may make one machine readable copy and/or one print copy for your personal use. You may also include very limited excerpts of 1stCommercialCredit.com content in printed memos, reports and presentations for internal, non-commercial use. We ask that you attribute this information to us by including "1st Commercial Credit, LLC. All rights reserved."Any other non-commercial use of 1st Commercial Credit content from any of its publications, research or web site requires written permission from us. All commercial uses of 1st Commercial Credit content requires our permission, including:• Use of 1st Commercial Credit content in advertisements or promotions• Use of 1st Commercial Credit trademarks or logos.• Use of quotes, excerpts or full text of 1st Commercial Credit articles, features or research.1st Commercial Credit, LLC provides this Internet site for the purpose of personal entertainment, information, education and communication. 1st Commercial Credit, LLC SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND THAT MAY ARISE FROM USE OF THIS SERVICE, INCLUDING: ERRORS OR OMISSIONS, CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING FROM THE USE OF ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIALS POSTED ON THIS SITE. 1st Commercial Credit, LLC reserves the right to change the terms and conditions of this agreement at any time.
